Come on out!
どうしたの？
出てきて！
My life, led lacking all splendor, is heading toward a climax.
華やかさとは無縁の　わが人生が
ここへきて　最高潮を迎えている
It's obvious!
決まりだろ！
Hey, come out of there!
ねえ　出てきて！
Hanuki-san is a woman with no faults on an emotional or visual level,
羽貫さんは　心情的にも　ビジュアル的にも
申し分ない女性だが
but tonight she was just too...
こよいの彼女は　あまりにも…
Carry me away, before that person comes...
わたしをさらって　あの人が来る前に
Kaori-san is a silent, lovely maiden.
香織さんは　無口で　かれんな乙女
However, we are fated to be apart!
しかし　彼女とわたしは　結ばれぬ運命
If we are not able to meet, then I cannot continue this relationship any longer.
「会えなければ
これ以上　関係を続けることは　できません」
Keiko-san is classy and ladylike, but I can't see her like that!
景子さんは　古風で　しとやかな女性
しかし　彼女には　おいそれと　会えない
I choose Kaori-san!
わたしは香織さんを選ぶ！
Why?!
何で？
hitobito wa atsui kumo ni kao wo kakushiteru
人々は厚い雲で顔を隠してる
Humans hide their faces in front of thick clouds
iki ba no nai omoi wo zutto motte toideiru
行き場のない想いをずっと持って研いでいる
Getting more and more consumed by the feeling of getting nowhere
nani mo nai machi ni umorete mo sore demo ima demo
何もない街に埋もれても それでも 今でも
Even now, they're still buried in the same empty town
tsuranaru uindou ni
連なるウィンドウに
A perfect dream of dolls lined up
narabitatsu ningyou no marui yume
並び立つ人形の悪い夢
on a stretched out window
sore to mo soko ni kakurete
それとも倉庫に隠れて
Then they hide themselves away
fusaidetatte
塞いでたって
so that they can be covered up
hokori dake kabutte mitsukaranai
埃だけ被って見つからない
Wearing only their pride, they still can't find anything
dare no te ni datte furerarenai
誰の手にだって触れられない
They still aren't touched, no matter whose hands they're in
boku tachi no genzai wo kurikaesu koto darake demo
僕たちの現在を繰り返すことだらけでも
If we repeat this moment of ours properly,
sou itsuka kimi to deaou
そういつか君と出会おう
I will meet you someday
sonna hi wo omotte hibi wo ikou
そんな日を思って 日々を行こう
Until that day is here, I will keep on going
ikou
行こう
Going
Then I was a brand-spanking new freshman university student
当時　ぴかぴかの大学１回生で　あった
わたしの目の前には
and before me were held out circles' fliers far surpassing my own information intake potential.
個人の情報量を　はるかに凌駕する
無数のサークルの　チラシが差し出され
そのどれもが
And through each of them I could see a gateway to that rose-colored campus life.
ばら色のキャンパスライフへの
扉で　あるかのように見えた
"Hero Show Association"
A four year moratorium.
４年間のモラトリアム　時に　アグレッシブに
Perhaps it would be good to grant children's aggressive dreams once in a while.
子供の夢を　かなえるのも　よいかもしれぬ
And perhaps a raven-haired maiden that understands young boys' dreams may appear!
少年の心を理解する　黒髪の乙女が　現れるかもしれぬ
I've turned over a new leaf!
心を洗われました
改心します
Please forgive me!
よし　よし！　ワッハッハ！
Excellent!
Now, everyone...
さあ　みんなで！
There you are, Mochiguman...
「そーれ　そーれ　モチグマン」
Never defeating anyone...
「誰も倒さず　誰も傷つけず」
Never hurting anyone...
Before you know it, trouble's quieted down...
「いつの間にか　もめ事　鎮め」
But he's strong...
「だけど　強いし
広い心　太い真心」
And has a big heart...
A great, big, sincere heart!
Hey, save Mochiguman!
あっ！　モチグマンを助けろ！
Oh, what's the matter?
あらら　どうしたの？
Those bad guys are trying to kidnap the girl, right?
お姉さんを　かどわかそうとした　悪者たちね
Everyone, make them change their ways!
さあ！　みんなで　改心させよう！
Change your ways! Change your ways! Change your ways!
改心しろ！　改心しろ！　改心しろ！
Change your ways! Change your ways!
Look, they ran away!
見て！　逃げてくぞ！
Good job, everyone!
よかった　よかった！
Looks like Mochiguman intervened yet again!
また　モチグマンが　とりなしたね
That's Mochiguman for you!
さすがだね！　モチグマン！
Oww...
痛てて…
I got knocked around pretty good there...
And it's only 3,000 yen a performance.
結構　本気で小突きやがって
ワンステ　３，０００円なのに
"I want to scout you. Big money guaranteed.
「君をスカウトしたい　高額保証」
「明日　正午　工学部の学食で
好きなものを頼んで　待っていたまえ」
Order what you'd like at the engineering cafeteria and wait tomorrow at noon."
Sounds pretty fishy to me.
何とも　いかがわしい
Thank you for earlier.
先ほどは　どうも
I spend my days in the Shimogamo Yuusuisou boarding house behind Eizan Demachiyanagi.
わたしが起居しているのは　えいざん出町柳裏にある
下鴨幽水荘という下宿である
今にも倒壊しそうな　木造　３階建て
It's a three-story wooden building that looks like it could collapse at any time.
It's so run-down that just looking at it is worrisome.
見る者を　やきもきさせる　おんぼろぶりは
もはや　重要文化財の境地だが
Perhaps it'll be an important cultural landmark soon,
これが消失して気にする人は
誰も　いないだろうことは　想像に難くない
but it's not difficult for me to imagine that no one would mind if it just vanished one day.
Dear viewers, be not surprised.
視聴者諸君　驚くなかれ
わたしは　ひょんなことから
I have been exchanging letters with a girl after some strange happenings.
ある女性と文通しているのだ
文通で肝心なのは　必ず手書きであるということ
The most crucial things about exchanging letters are that they be handwritten
地獄の釜が開こうとも　相手に会っては
ならないということである
and that you never meet your partner in correspondence,
even should the very cauldron of hell be unleashed.
Far too oft that the elegant, precious
大切に培ってきた　優雅な関係が一瞬にして
水泡に帰すること大だ
relationship you had fostered vanishes in an instant.
Her name is Higuchi Keiko-san, and I can tell her intelligence and education from her letters.
彼女の名前は　樋口　景子さんといい
文面から　知性と教養が　におい立つ
わたしの理想像と　いうべき女性である
She is surely my ideal woman.
So, what should I do?
さて　どうしたものか
What does it matter?
どうだって　いいんじゃね！
You speak of this to no one.
これは　絶対　他言無用
最高機密で　お願いしたいんだが
I'd like you to keep it top secret.
You see, I want you to be a certain woman's bodyguard.
君に　ある女性の　ボディーガードを頼みたい
B-Bodyguard?
ボ…　ボディーガード？
It's not a dangerous job.
危険な仕事ではない
You just need to protect her while I am gone.
わたしの留守を　守ってくれさえすればいいんだ
There's been some... trouble lately.
特に最近　何かと物騒だ
There are a great number of people who would try to deceive me.
わたしを陥れようとしている　人間も　ごまんといる
But you, my friend, I can rely on without reservation.
君なら安心して　この仕事を任せられる
You're as safe a bet as they come, yes?
筋金入りの　安全パイだろう？
石橋を粉々に　たたき壊してしまう奥手と聞いている
I hear you're a late bloomer that is exceedingly shy.
Therefore I have no need to worry about you doing anything... funny.
妙な気を　起こす心配もないわけだ
Will you handle this?
やってくれるかい？
Let me introduce you.
紹介しよう
This is Kaori.
香織だ
Kaori is a very elegant woman.
香織は　とても　エレガントな女性だ
I want you to be very courteous to her.
丁重に接してほしい
But I do not wish the world at large to learn of our private matters.
しかし　われわれの　プライバシーが
広く世間に　流布することは好まん！
If you speak about this to others, then, for you...
もし　このことを他言したら　君など…
His name was Jougasaki, and he was the president of the movie circle Misogi.
男は城ヶ崎といい
映画サークル　「ＭＩＳＯＧＩ」の　会長なのであった
香織　接待マニュアルなるものを渡された
He handed me Kaori's entertainment manual.
Things like no direct contact, her favorite drinks,
直接　触ってはいけない
好きな飲み物　菓子を切らさず
not to run out of sweets, show her movies to make sure she doesn't get bored...
退屈させないように　映画を見せて　あげるようになど
必須内容が指導された
All the essential principles were written down.
Well, I'm counting on you.
じゃあ　留守をよろしく頼む
Don't go getting any weird thoughts, now.
変な気　起こすなよ！
I couldn't think of her as a doll at all.
とても　人形とは思えない
Her hair was carefully combed, and her clothes were neat and elegant.
彼女の髪は　奇麗に　なでつけられ
きちんと　上品な服を着ていた
化粧　つめの手入れ　肌艶よく
Her makeup, and fingernails, and skin were all lovely...
この気品のある表情は　どうであろうか
Where did that elegant expression come from?
It!
は…　早く　城ヶ崎氏が帰ってくるといいね
...would be nice if Mr. Jougasaki came home soon, yes?
That Jougasaki is really a very simple and good person, don't you think?
城ヶ崎って人は　ホントは単純な　いい人なのかな
You are beautiful...
君は美しいね
城ヶ崎氏の気持ちが　分からぬでもない
It's not like I can't understand how Mr. Jougasaki feels.
わたしは生身の女性が　いいと思うが
Although I do think I'd prefer a flesh and blood woman...
And so the days where I would receive
そうして　城ヶ崎氏の留守を守っては
給料をもらう日々が続いた
payment for guarding while Mr. Jougasaki was out continued.
When Mr. Jougasaki came back, I would be quickly thrown out of the room.
城ヶ崎氏が帰ってくると
わたしは　入れ違いに　部屋を追い出される
Those days...
そんな日々が
What's with you lately?
どうすか　最近は？　何だか　羽振りが良さそうですが
Seems like you've been moving up in the world.
I don't know what you mean.
何もないよ
You're Kaori-san's bodyguard, isn't that right?
う～ん　おおかた　香織さんのボディーガード料でしょう
なっ　なぜ　それを？
H-How do you know that?
Please do not underestimate my information-gathering network.
わたしの情報網を　甘く見てはいけませんよ
Jougasaki-san may act that way, but he's really pure-hearted.
城ヶ崎さんは　ああ見えて　純情な男ですからね
What do you mean?
どういうことだ
That is a very refined kind of love.
あれは　とても高尚な愛の形なのです
そこらのダッチワイフとは　訳が違う
It's a far cry from some "dutch wife."
超高級品ですぞ　ラブドールと呼ぶのです
It's a very high-quality product called a "love doll."
Meaning that it's designed to be loved and held dear by its owner.
相手のことを思い　大切にめでながら
暮らすことに意味があるのです
あなたのように　性欲処理の　道具にしか
見てない野人には　分からないでしょうが
A boor like you who thinks of it as nothing more
than a tool to satisfy one's sexual desire wouldn't understand.
Shut up, right now!
今すぐ　黙れ！　未来永劫　黙れ！
And then stay silent for eternity!
Oh, I'll have to decline.
それは　お断りです
If I can't chat, I'll be so lonely I'll die!
僕は　無駄口が利けないと　寂しくて死ぬのです
Sounds good to me!
死ねばよいのだ
On the other hand, I won't die as long as I'm making some idle chatter.
ところがどっこい　無駄口を利いているかぎり
僕は死なないのです
I have no empathy for a soulless being like you.
わたしは　魂の入ってないものに　感情移入などしない
Be a bit more honest with yourself, will you?
素直じゃないですね　あなたも
Mr. Jougasaki seemed to be busy at the moment shooting a film.
城ヶ崎氏は　今　映画の撮影で　忙しいらしく
It was a modern remake of Alexander the Great
撮っている映画は　現代版　『アレキサンダー大王』とも
いうべき　自身の集大成の映画らしい
which was supposed to be the culmination of his work or something.
Within his circle he was very popular and charismatic,
サークルでは　カリスマとして通っており
とてもモテるものの
but his favorite was, of course, Kaori-san.
やはり本命は　香織さんということだった
Well, I'm counting on you.
じゃ　よろしくな
Around this time Mr. Jougasaki would be out of his room continuously,
このところ　部屋を空ける日が　続いている城ヶ崎氏
ふびんな身の上である彼女に
つい　親身になってしまうが
and feeling sorry for the girl, I took tender care of her...
Although, of course, she was just a doll.
そうはいっても　彼女は人形である
I am exchanging letters with a real flesh and blood woman.
わたしは　生身の女性と　文通しているのだ
彼女は　ちゃんと返事をくれる
She always answers me back.
No matter how beautiful Kaori-san looks to the eye, she will never respond.
香織さんは　見た目が　いくら美しくても
返事をしてくれることはない
Hey...
はい？
Yes?
Hey... Hey...
The exquisite workmanship,
作りが精巧であることと　城ヶ崎氏の
つくりあげた　繊細かつ　かれんな世界は
and the delicate and lovely world Jougasaki had set up,
時々　彼女を　本当の人間のように思わせた
made me think of her as a real person occasionally.
OZ news is going great, don't you think?
ＯＺニュース　絶好調じゃない
羽貫さんのおかげですよ
It's all thanks to you, Hanuki-san.
Hanuki-san is a dental hygienist and an older member of the English Conversation circle.
羽貫さんは　歯科衛生士であり
英会話サークルの先輩である
サークルの後　毎回　カフェで
お茶をするのが習慣となっていた
It became a habit of ours to go to a café after each session.
But it seemed like she only drank alcohol with people she knew well,
しかし　気の知れた人としか　酒を飲まないらしく
わたしは　いまだ　飲みに誘われたことはなかった
and I had not yet been asked out for drinks.
彼女は　エロ歯科医　窪塚からの　ひっきりなしの誘いと
She was wavering between the perverted dentist, Kubouzuka,
ほったらかしの彼氏の間で　揺れていた
who continuously asked her out, and a boyfriend that neglected her.
I finally received a letter from my pen-pal Keiko-san saying she wanted to meet.
文通相手の景子さんから
とうとう　「会いたい」と　手紙が来てしまった
I suppose that's proof that my literary skills
乙女の心に　火を付けてしまったのは
わたしの文才が並々ならぬことの　証しであろう
at lighting a maiden's heart on fire were nothing to scoff at.
However, I was not able to meet her.
しかし　わたしは　会うわけにはいかなかった
なぜなら　手紙の中のわたしは　少しばかり
現実の　わたしに比べて　美しく飾られていたからである
Why? Because the me within the letters was ever so slightly embellished from the me in reality.
確かに　それは　わたしの理想とする
男性像では　あるものの
It's true that's what I envision my ideal self to be,
but it will take a bit of time for the current me to catch up.
現実のわたしが　それに追い付くには
今　しばらく　時間が必要であった
It's an emergency!
緊急事態だ！
Man, your place stinks!
臭いなあ　お前んち
しかし　俺の下宿は　どうにも物騒だ
But my place isn't safe.
香織を　ここで　しばらく預かってくれ
Hold on to Kaori here for a while, will you?
Kaori, I'm sorry. I know this is a filthy place, but please endure it for a little while.
香織　ごめんね　薄汚い所だけど
しばらくの辛抱だから
I'll pay you the same hourly rate as before, at 24 hours a day.
時給は　これまでと同じで　２４時間分　出す
しかし　手元にないから　銀行振り込みにさせてくれ
However, I don't have the cash on hand, so please allow me to do a direct bank deposit.
That was how Kaori-san and I began living together.
こうして　わたしと香織さんの　同棲生活が始まった
And wait, wasn't Mr. Jougasaki thinking a bit too little of me?
それにしても　城ヶ崎氏は　わたしのことを
軽んじ過ぎてやしないか？
Be that as it may, I never even dreamed that
とはいえ　まさか　こんな甘い生活が　わたしの
キャンパスライフに訪れるとは　夢にも思わなかった
such a sweet campus life would be visited upon me.
たんたんと暮らしてきた　これまでの２年間
身辺が　これだけ　華やいだことはなかった
In these two past years I'd spent living uneventfully,
I had never experienced such a brilliant event.
This and that... And two of each, please.
これと　あれと
あ…　それを２つずつ下さい
When I returned from class, Kaori-san was waiting for me in my room.
学校から帰ってくれば　香織さんが部屋で待っている
That alone made the days enjoyable.
それだけでも　楽しい日々
It was as if an intellectual, raven-haired maiden
まるで彼女は　わたしの部屋の一隅を借りて
小説に夢を膨らませる　知的な黒髪の乙女のようだった
whose dreams were filled with novels had borrowed a corner of my room.
One of these days she will no longer be here, will she?
いつか　彼女は　ここから　いなくなるときが
来るのだろうか？
They say love comes on all forms,
愛の形は　様々だというものの
ここまで　閉鎖的な愛の迷路に
迷いこんだら　危険である
but it is dangerous to become lost in the maze of such an insular love.
帰り道が分からなくなる恐れが　ありながら
As I became fearful that I could no longer find the exit, I pressed deeper along the path.
わたしは　道の奥へと　入りこんでいた
決めちゃいな！
Just do it!
I am pleased to eat ramen for the first time.
初めてのラーメン　うれしゅうございます
I always wished to eat it once.
一度　食べてみとうございました
あなたの　お口に　合いますかどうか
I'm not sure whether it's to your taste, however...
She's quite beautiful, yes?
すごい　美人でしょう
However, she's Jougasaki's girlfriend, so please keep it a secret that we came here to eat.
城ヶ崎さんの彼女ですが
ここへ食べにきたことは　内緒ですよ
さあ　食べましょう
So, eat up.
A dream?
夢
Hey, you ate ramen! I can smell it on you!
おいっ！　ラーメン食っただろ！　においが付いてるぞ
Don't eat in your room! Eat outside!
家で食事するな！　外で食え！
But well, I'm not getting any younger.
しかし　俺も　もう　いい年だ
これまで　好き勝手なことをしてきたが
I've just been doing what I felt like up till now,
but when I finish this movie I'm filming, I'm thinking of settling down.
今　撮っている映画が完成したら　身を固めようと思う
卒業　就職する
I'll graduate, get a job, and then live once again with Kaori.
そして　また　香織と一緒に　暮らそうと思う
You've been a great help.
君には　世話になったな
近く　香織を迎えに来る　じゃあな
I'll come to pick up Kaori soon.
See you later.
Finally I received an ultimatum from Keiko-san.
とうとう　景子さんから　最後通達が来てしまった
If I don't meet with her this time, all communication will likely cease.
これで会わなければ　今後
一切　連絡が途絶えてしまうであろう
But I was still not the man able to see Keiko-san.
しかし　わたしは　まだまだ
景子さんに会える身ではなかった
Hey, wanna go for some drinks?
どう？　今日　飲みに行かない？
Um...
今日は　大事なリポートがあって
I have a report I need to write today...
Oh, I see.
そっか
Right. Good luck on your report!
うん　分かった　リポート　頑張ってね
And finally I was asked out for drinks by Hanuki-san as proof that we were close,
とうとう　待ちに待った　羽貫さんと
親しい間柄という　お墨付きの　飲みの誘いなのに
yet I ended up going home.
わたしは　帰ってきてしまった
Why? Because tonight was the night Jougasaki was coming to pick up Kaori-san.
なぜなら　城ヶ崎氏が　香織さんを
引き取りに来るのも　今夜であった
Unless I aim to become come Renaissance man of the sexual arts,
八面六臂の　桃色遊戯の達人でなければ
誰か　一人に　絞らねばならない
I must narrow it down to one of them.
Kaori-san, please wait a little while!
香織さん　ちょっと待ってておくれ！
これは　人命救助だ！
This is a matter of life and death!
羽貫さんが　エロ歯科医の毒牙に
かかってしまいかねない！
I cannot allow Hanuki-san to be ruined by some perverted dentist's intentions!
However, at the hotel's lounge I was met with an expected turn of events.
しかし　ホテルのラウンジでは
予想外の展開が待っていた
そこには　何と　城ヶ崎氏の姿があった
For there in front of me was Mr. Jougasaki.
香織さんという人が　ありながら
Disgusted that he would try and place his hands on Hanuki-san while he was still with Kaori-san,
羽貫さんにまで手を出そうとは
純情が聞いてあきれる
I knew I had no choice but to win this drinking battle!
この飲み比べ　決して　負けるわけにはいかない！
Somehow, I was victorious!
どうにか勝負には　勝った
And then...
ところが…
And then I was met with yet another unexpected turn of events.
ところが　この後　まったく
想定外の展開が　待っているのだった
Open up!
開けて！
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
おーい　何やってんだ！　いくしかないだろ！
We've got to do this!
This is our once in a lifetime chance!
千載一遇の大チャンスだろー！
I knew it... Kaori's the only one for me....
やはり　わたしには　香織しかいない
Kaori!
香織！
ええっ！？
Kaori!
香織！
My body shakes thinking this might be the last time I hear your voice.
今生の聞き納めとあらば　あなたの声に
体が震えます
If I am loved once more by Jougasaki, a different me will surely sprout.
再び　城ヶ崎にめでられれば違う草木になりましょう
The me who is here now only exists in front of you.
今の　わたしでいるのは　あなたの　前だけです
香織…
Kaori...
Please take me with you and escape.
わたしを連れて　逃げてください！
Please, please!
お願い　お願い
"We're eloping. Thank you for everything. - Kaori," eh?
「かけおちします　今まで　ありがとう　香織」ね～
Oh, Jougasaki-san?
あっ　城ヶ崎さん？
香織さん　ぬれてしまう
Kaori-san is getting wet!
I'm sorry, Kaori-san...
ごめんね　香織さん
It's okay. I'm glad. I've never gotten wet from the rain before.
ううん　いいの　わたし　うれしいの
雨にぬれるのは　初めてなんですもの
Kaori-san...
香織さん…
You there, student...
学生さん
うわあ！
The old woman!
お…　おばあ！
Student, what might you wish to ask?
学生さん　何を　お聞きになりたいんでしょう？
わたしは　何も　尋ねていない！
I haven't asked you anything!
I see. You are dissatisfied, yes?
なるほど
あなたは不満なのですね
I said I had no idea what you're talking about!
だから　わたしは　知らんと言っている！
However, opportunity is always dangling in front of you.
とにかく　好機は　いつでも
あなたの　目の前に　ぶら下がってございます
Please grab on to it.
それを　つかまえてごらんなさい
はい　７，０００円
That'll be 7,000 yen.
Hey, what are you doing?
おい　何をする！
When the rain lets up,
雨がやんだら　京都駅へ行って
we'll head to Kyoto station and buy train tickets to as far away as we can.
ここから　一番　遠く離れた駅まで　切符を買おう
Then we'll head to a country at the end of the earth,
そこから　最果ての国へ行き
and live in a small town in a small house...
小さな町の　小さな家に住もう
Working in a strange land will surely be tough,
慣れない土地での　仕事は大変だろうが
君の笑顔を見れば　元気が出る
but seeing your smile when I come home will give me cheer.
Before long, we'll have a child,
やがて　子供ができたら
反対していた両親も　きっと　認めてくれるだろう
and your parents who were against this will surely come to accept me.
The days and months pass by and at length we have grandchildren.
月日は流れて　やがて　わたしにも　孫ができる
この日のために　生きてきたのだと気付き　涙するのだ
As I realize I have lived only for that day, tears fall from my eyes.
最高に　幸せな日々
They are the happiest days of my life.
But suddenly you fall ill, and I grasp your hand, nursing you.
でも　突然　君が病気になり
わたしは手を握り　看病し続ける
Smiling, you say "I'm so glad I met you."
君は　笑って　こう言う
「あなたに　出会えて　よかった」
それは　まさに　わたしのせりふだ
But no, that's what I should be saying!
わたしが　先にいく　約束ではなかったのか
Didn't we promise that I'd be the first to go?
しかし　君と一緒になれてよかった
I'm just so glad we were able to be together!
If this isn't an opportunity, then what is?
こ…　これを　好機と言わずして　何と　言おうか？
Hey now, this here's a 100% full-blow opportunity!
おい　おい！　これ　１００％　好機到来じゃん！
Look at her face, she's waiting for you!
彼女の顔　見てみろよ？　待ってるぜ！
Kaori-san isn't like that!
香織さんは　そんな人じゃない！
No matter how high-class her face looks,
いくら　品のいい顔をしてても
心の中は　熱くたぎって　お前と同じ思いなんだ！
inside her heart is the same burning passion that's inside yours!
That's a lie!
嘘だ
Hell no it isn't!
嘘なもんか！
なぜ　彼女はお前に　ついてきた？
Why do you think she came with you?
ずっと　ついてきたぞ！
She's always with you!
See? She's been looking at you the whole time...
ほら　ずっと　お前を見ている！
Before we part, I want to share your warmth...
お別れする前に　あなたの　ぬくもりを　分けてください
Would you let me feel like I am loved?
わたしを　愛した証しを　感じさせてくださいまし
Kaori-san, but...
香織さん　しかし
I know that to you this isn't passionate, burning love.
あなたにとって　身を焦がすような
恋ではないことは　知っておりました
But right now the warmth of your hand
しかし　今はあなたの　手のぬくもりが
is the one thing that can make me feel like I'm alive.
唯一　わたしが　今　生きていることを
感じさせてくれます
You can't? Is it because I'm not a real person?
駄目？
わたしが　生身の人間ではないから？
Because I'm a doll without a heart?
心のない人形だから？
No, Kaori-san! That's not it!
いや　香織さん
そんなことはないんだ！　わたしだって
I also...
I... I...
わたしは　わたしは…
You're too beautiful!
美し過ぎる！
逃げるな　腰抜けが！
Don't run away, you coward!
ずっと　貧弱奥手野郎のままで　いいのか？
You want to spend the rest of your life a pitiful late-bloomer?
安全パイと　呼ばれ続けていいのか？
You're okay with being called a "safe bet"?
彼女に恥をかかせるな！
Don't worry about her shame!
I think she wants you to thrust your burning passion upon her!
お前のたぎる情熱を　ぶつけてほしいと思ってるんだ！
ずっと　待ってるんだぞ！
She's been waiting this whole time!
It's okay, I'm sorry.
いいの　ごめんなさい
I am, after all, a doll.
しょせん　わたしは　人形
彼女を女にしてやれ！
Then make her a woman!
No, I can't do it!
駄目だ　わたしにはできない！
Then you come and do it!
じゃあ　あなたが　来て！
Got it... I'll do it for him...
分かった　俺が　代わりにやってやる
Come to me!
来て！
Stop! What are you doing?
よせ！　何をする！
Come!
来てよー！
Kaori-san! Johnny, stop it!
香織さん！
やめろジョニー！
チェスト～！
Kaori!
香織！　香織　香織
Kaori, Kaori!
You sick bastard!
この　変態野郎ー！
This is how it should be.
これで　いいのだ
I had almost lost my pure heart.
危うく　純潔を失うところだった
わたしは　きっと　香織さんを　清らかに　愛しきれない
I would never have been able to love Kaori-san in a pure manner.
It is a path unable to be tread by we normal people.
これは　やはり　凡人には
踏み入れられない　領域なのだ
城ヶ崎氏と　香織さん
そのまま　あなた方の道を進め！
Jougasaki and Kaori-san, keep going down that path together!
I wonder if Keiko-san waited for me at the place she said?
景子さんは　待ち合わせの場所で待っていたのか？
やはり　一番　優先するべきは
彼女ではなかったか？
Perhaps she was the preferable choice?
I want to return to that scene once again!
もう一度　あのシーンへ戻りたい
リテーク
Retake!
I want to meet Keiko-san!
景子さんに会いたい！
tengoku iku tame mainichi kosotto
天国　いくため　毎日こそっと
In order to go to heaven. Everyday, I quietly
naishou de ii koto shiteta kedo
内緒で　いいこと　してたけど
and privately do good deeds
namida hitohira
涙ひとひら
But a single teardrop
atama kurakura
あたまくらくら
Sends my head spinning
ano ko hasuppa koi dorobou
あの娘　はすっぱ　恋泥棒
That stupid girl, that love thief
watashi kenage ii hito
わたしけなげ　いいひと
I am a good and pure person
kanawanakatta koigokoro
叶わなかった恋心
My longing heart was not fulfilled
kamisama doushite
神様どうして
Why, god?
yurusanakucha koi dorobou
ゆるさなくっちゃ恋泥棒
I must forgive her. That love thief
ano ko tabun ii hito
あの娘たぶん　いいひと
Maybe she was actually a good person
wasurenakucha konna koto
忘れなくっちゃこんなこと
I have to forget all these things
watashi wa tengoku
わたしは天国
I'm in heaven
yurusanakucha
ゆるさなくっちゃ
I have to forgive her!